apnaindia.com 2015-05-25

# ApnaIndia.com,Classifieds|India Yellow pages|Jobs|Videos|News|Cricket|Movie Updates

This Privacy Policy sets out our practices with respect to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information in connection with apnaindia.com. This Privacy Policy may be updated by us at any time by posting on the site without any prior notice. Also, this Privacy Statement may be supplemented or modified by agreements entered into between us and an individual from time to time. In this Privacy Statement, personal information means any information about an identifiable individual, including contact and demographic details, not including collective information or information regarding a group in summarized form.

Personal Information: 

All the users are required to provide us their contact information and demographic information in order to be registered with the site or to become permanent or temporary members. Contact information would mean the information such as name, mailing address, mobile no etc; Demographic information would mean information such as age, occupation, income level etc;The customer contact information is collected only for the sake of registration and will be used only to contact the customer in terms of the services offered by apnaindia.com.

The Website may publish the contact details of the customers who volunteer or shows willingness to participate in the ad campaign by the site. After publishing your contact details, we cease to accept responsibility as how the other viewers may utilize your contact information. We have no control over who views online or print ads. Contact information provided may be used to contact customers when necessary.

apnaindia.com may also collect customer's financial information (such as account or credit card numbers) to bill the user for products and services of their choice. However, we retain this information only as needed to process the transaction within the preview of law.

The Website uses the demographic data to match each visitor's experience at the Site. This includes displaying the content as per the user.s preference. This may include our study about the user group in displaying the content. We also conduct online surveys which may ask the visitors for the contact information. Such information will be used to update users about our products and services. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings. We may use customer information for additional purposes that may be identified at or before the time that the information is collected. We also use information from customers for accounting and transaction completion purposes.

apnaindia.com uses third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about products and services of interest to you.

Disclosure :

We may disclose certain personal information by publishing ads either online and or in print also to the third party service providers. It's our obligation to disclose your personal information to the Law enforcement authorities to facilitate investigations against fraud or any other offense. During the reorganization phase of the company which includes sale, we may disclose your personal information to legal, financial and related professional agencies and advisory boards.

You will agree to receive SMS from the visitors and other users through the site by listing your mobile number on apnaindia.com.

Except as provided above, we will not use or disclose personal information for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required or permitted by law.

Cookies and IP Addresses :

apnaindia.com may track and use your IP address to certify your membership, gather broad demographic information about our users, diagnose problems with our server, and administer the Site effectively. The Site uses relevant cookies to keep track of your membership tools and to make sure you do not see the same ad repeatedly. Cookies will be used to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so as to avoid repeating the credentialing process. By doing so you need not re-enter it each time you visit the Site. We also provide an option to log out when you are using an insecure or shared computer. We allow external ad companies to display ads containing cookies on the Site.

Links : 

apnaindia.com contains links to other websites, such as websites providing search capabilities and information resources designed to inform buyers and sellers about general aspects of property that is being sold. We do not assume responsibility for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. It's your prerogative to review the privacy policies of the websites that you visit.

Opting Out :

apnaindia.com gives its users an unconditional option for Opting Out. You may opt out from receiving communication and remove your information from our database. You may also opt out from receiving any service of any nature and capacity form The Website.You may contact us any time during your visit to the site in order to Opt Out.
